<!-- DO NOT MODIFY THIS FILE. -->
<!-- This entire file was automatically generated by PublishConfiguration.csproj. -->
<!-- Make any needed changes in PublishConfiguration.csproj. -->

<Publish>
    <!-- Mod ID is not required for publishing a mod for the first time.  Mod ID must be set in order to update an existing mod. -->
    <ModId Value="88157" />

    <!-- Name of the mod to display to players.  Copied from assembly Title. -->
    <DisplayName Value="Extra Hotkeys" />

    <!-- Short description of the mod.  Copied from assembly Description. -->
    <ShortDescription Value="This mod adds extra hotkeys to the game that should have been there by default." />

    <!-- Long description of the mod.  Copied from ReadMe.md file.  Supports minimal markdown subset. -->
    <LongDescription>
# ExtraHotkeys
A mod for Cities: Skylines 2 that adds extra hotkeys and quality of life improvements to the game that should have been there in the first place.

## Changelog+
* **V1.0.2.**
	* Added brush size and strength scrollwheel actions for tree brush
	* Fixed minor typo in the settings menu
* **v1.0.1**
  * Potential bugfix for freezing keyboard when playing in windowed mode
  * Some refactoring and cleanup of the codebase
* **v1.0.0** 		
  * Added scrollwheel support for various quality of life improvements like controlling the road elevation, brush size and -strength in the terrain tool, etc.
* **v0.2.0**
  * Added hotkeys for tool modes and snapping options.
* **v0.1.0**
  * Initial release.

## Features
- Adds hotkeys for opening tool windows (like road, zoning, etc.).
- Adds hotkeys for selecting tool modes and snapping options.
- All hotkeys can be customized in the game options menu.
- Adds scrollwheel support for various quality of life improvements like controlling the road elevation, brush size and -strength in the terrain tool, etc.

## Instructions
- Install the mod from the Paradox Mods website, Skyve or the in-game mod browser.
- Go to the options menu in the game.
- Click on the "Extra Hotkeys" tab.
- Customize the hotkeys to your liking.
- Check the settings in the "General" tab to enable the scrollwheel support options. The description should explain what each option does.

## Todo
- Add language support. Currently, only English is supported.
- Add more hotkeys (suggestions are welcome).

## Credits
- This mod is inspired by the discontinued mod "ExtendedHotkeys" by [89pleasure](https://github.com/89pleasure).
- Thanks to **rcav8tr** for the [CS2-Modding-Instructions](https://github.com/rcav8tr/CS2-Modding-Instructions) which helped me 
to kickstart my modding journey.

## Personal Note
I made this mod because I was tired of having to click on the toolbar to select the tools. Cities Skylines 1 had way more 
hotkeys than the sequel by default. And since I spend a few hundred hours in CS:1 , I got used to open the tools with hotkeys. 
So I decided to make this mod to add some of the hotkeys that I missed in CS:2. I hope you enjoy it! Feel free to suggest
more hotkeys or features that you would like to see in this mod. 

I'm a long time web developer, but I just started to learn C# and Unity ECS a short time ago, so the code may not be the best 
or most efficient, but at least it works. This is my first mod for Cities Skylines 2, so I'm still learning. :-)

If you find this mod useful, please consider buying me a coffee or something. :-) Check the PayPal link on the right side. 
Of course, this is totally optional!
</LongDescription>

    <!-- Thumbnail. -->
    <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />

    <!-- Screenshot.  Copied from Screenshots folder.  Include no spaces in file names.  Max file size is 2.1MB.  Can be set multiple times. -->
    <Screenshot Value="Properties\Screenshots\10-open_tool_windows.png" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties\Screenshots\20-set_tool_modes.png" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties\Screenshots\30-quality_of_live_settings.png" />


    <!-- Tag.  Can be set multiple times. -->
    <Tag Value="Code Mod" />

    <!-- Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed. -->
    <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/extra-hotkeys.1700331/" />

    <!-- Version of the mod.  Copied from assembly Version. -->
    <ModVersion Value="1.0.2" />

    <!-- Recommended version of the base game to use the mod. -->
    <GameVersion Value="1.*" />

    <!-- Change log.  Copied from ChangeLog.md file.  Supports minimal markdown subset. -->
    <ChangeLog>
- Added brush size and strength scrollwheel actions for tree brush
- Fixed minor typo in the settings menu
</ChangeLog>

    <!-- External links. Supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon.  Can be set multiple times. -->
    <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/Fenrir200678/ExtraHotkeys" />
    <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/Uukmqvy8" />
    <ExternalLink Type="paypal" Url="https://www.paypal.com/paypalme/fenrir200678" />
</Publish>
